{
    "cities": [
        {
            "id": "3274",
            "cityName": "Arnavutkoy",
            "country": "Turkiye",
            "emoji": "ðŸ‡¹ðŸ‡·",
            "date": "2024-03-05T20:10:02.911Z",
            "notes": "",
            "position": {
                "lat": 41.18357363199765,
                "lng": 28.741950988769535
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "94a1",
            "cityName": "Istanbul",
            "country": "Turkiye",
            "emoji": "ðŸ‡¹ðŸ‡·",
            "date": "2024-03-05T20:10:13.839Z",
            "notes": "",
            "position": {
                "lat": 41.009971313794296,
                "lng": 28.95601272583008
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "04e8",
            "cityName": "Odunpazari",
            "country": "Turkiye",
            "emoji": "ðŸ‡¹ðŸ‡·",
            "date": "2024-03-05T20:10:28.151Z",
            "notes": "",
            "position": {
                "lat": 39.76846413894052,
                "lng": 30.51864624023438
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "9426",
            "cityName": "Sehitkamil",
            "country": "Turkiye",
            "emoji": "ðŸ‡¹ðŸ‡·",
            "date": "2024-03-05T20:11:29.367Z",
            "notes": "",
            "position": {
                "lat": 37.08694870883852,
                "lng": 37.395744323730476
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "1f42",
            "cityName": "Selcuklu",
            "country": "Turkiye",
            "emoji": "ðŸ‡¹ðŸ‡·",
            "date": "2024-03-05T20:11:48.373Z",
            "notes": "",
            "position": {
                "lat": 37.92824717265132,
                "lng": 32.506828308105476
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "7b48",
            "cityName": "Ankara",
            "country": "Turkiye",
            "emoji": "ðŸ‡¹ðŸ‡·",
            "date": "2023-09-14T20:14:33.000Z",
            "notes": "GÃ¼zeldi",
            "position": {
                "lat": 39.91975004458887,
                "lng": 32.85409927368165
            }
        },
        {
            "id": "38bf",
            "cityName": "Madrid",
            "country": "Spain",
            "emoji": "ðŸ‡ªðŸ‡¸",
            "date": "2024-03-12T20:42:30.526Z",
            "notes": "gÃ¼zeldi",
            "position": {
                "lat": 40.36807346666197,
                "lng": -3.6914062500000004
            }
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which is the most popular JavaScript framework?",
      "options": ["Angular", "React", "Svelte", "Vue"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company invented React?",
      "options": ["Google", "Apple", "Netflix", "Facebook"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the fundamental building block of React apps?",
      "options": ["Components", "Blocks", "Elements", "Effects"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the name of the syntax we use to describe the UI in React components?",
      "options": ["FBJ", "Babel", "JSX", "ES2015"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How does data flow naturally in React apps?",
      "options": [
        "From parents to children",
        "From children to parents",
        "Both ways",
        "The developers decides"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How to pass data into a child component?",
      "options": ["State", "Props", "PropTypes", "Parameters"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "When to use derived state?",
      "options": [
        "Whenever the state should not trigger a re-render",
        "Whenever the state can be synchronized with an effect",
        "Whenever the state should be accessible to all components",
        "Whenever the state can be computed from another state variable"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What triggers a UI re-render in React?",
      "options": [
        "Running an effect",
        "Passing props",
        "Updating state",
        "Adding event listeners to DOM elements"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "When do we directly \"touch\" the DOM in React?",
      "options": [
        "When we need to listen to an event",
        "When we need to change the UI",
        "When we need to add styles",
        "Almost never"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "In what situation do we use a callback to update state?",
      "options": [
        "When updating the state will be slow",
        "When the updated state is very data-intensive",
        "When the state update should happen faster",
        "When the new state depends on the previous state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "If we pass a function to useState, when will that function be called?",
      "options": [
        "On each re-render",
        "Each time we update the state",
        "Only on the initial render",
        "The first time we update the state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hook to use for an API request on the component's initial render?",
      "options": ["useState", "useEffect", "useRef", "useReducer"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which variables should go into the useEffect dependency array?",
      "options": [
        "Usually none",
        "All our state variables",
        "All state and props referenced in the effect",
        "All variables needed for clean up"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "An effect will always run on the initial render.",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "It depends on the dependency array",
        "False",
        "In depends on the code in the effect"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "When will an effect run if it doesn't have a dependency array?",
      "options": [
        "Only when the component mounts",
        "Only when the component unmounts",
        "The first time the component re-renders",
        "Each time the component is re-rendered"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
    
}
